Guide to the Larry Kramer Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- October 2008 Acquisition, circa 1916-2008; 100.38; (116 boxes) + 2 broadside folders, 8 rolls, 2 record albums
  - Audiovisual Material, circa 1967-1990s
    - Videocassettes, circa 1980s-1990s
      - Larry Kramer, Albany Healthcare Workers, 1993 November; YCALMSS722_0012; 1; 00:59:23 (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102337616)
      - BBC The Late Show, Out in America, undated; YCALMSS722_0013; 1; 00:43:31; NTSC (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102337624)
      - Testing the Limits, 28 minutes, undated; YCALMSS722_0014; 1; 00:32:21 (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102337632)
      - AIDS Quarterly, 1989 Winter; YCALMSS722_0015; 1; 00:45:00 (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102337640)
      - Hoffman-Laroche Community Advisory Board Action: Marriot Marquis, New York City, 1993 January 16; YCALMSS722_0016; 1 (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102337657)
      - Newsmaker Sunday, 1993 April 25; YCALMSS722_0017; 1; 00:28:11 (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102337665)
      - Arena: Larry Kramer (Kramer v Kramer) 60 minutes, undated; YCALMSS722_0018; 1; 00:55:09 (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102337673)
      - Nightline, ABC News, 1991 November 7; YCALMSS722_0019; 1; 00:47:01 (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102337681)
      - Target Bush (AIDS Community Television), 1993; YCALMSS722_0020; 1; 00:29:44 (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102416899)
      - The Normal Heart, Hollywood Playhouse, 1989 December 14; YCALMSS722_0021; 1; 02:39:27 (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102416907)
      - The Normal Heart, reading Cape Cod, recorded by Tim McCarthy, undated; YCALMSS722_0022; 1; 02:39:11 (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102416915)
      - The Normal Heart, Southern Utah University, Ana Dittmar, 1991 May 6; YCALMSS722_0023; 1; 00:05:05 (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102416923)
      - The Normal Heart, P.M. (PM Magazine), undated; YCALMSS722_0024; 1; 00:56:08 (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102416931)
        "Normal Heart" segment runs 00:04:45 in length. The rest of the tape is media coverage of the U.S. strike against Libya.
      - Larry Kramer Interview and ATAC Opening Speech, recorded by Tim McCarthy, 1990 November 10; YCALMSS722_0025; 1; 00:46:52; The audio is a little bit low. (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102416949)
      - Larry Kramer, BBCtv, part one, 1993 August 19; YCALMSS722_0026; 1; 02:22:35 (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102416956)
      - Larry Kramer, BBCtv, part two, 1993 August 20; YCALMSS722_0027; 1; 00:33:04 (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102416964)
      - Larry Kramer/Kathleen Sullivan CBS Morning Show, 1989 November 30; YCALMSS722_0028; 1; 02:04:29 (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102416972)
      - Gay Pride Weekend, Statue of Liberty, Fireworks, Shelter Island Garden, 1990; YCALMSS722_0029; 1; 03:58:54 (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102416980)
      - Roger McFarlane/Larry Kramer GMHC 81-99, Hunter College Graduate School of Public Health, 1988 November; YCALMSS722_0030; 1; 01:43:10 (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102416998)
      - 0054-2054 Sources 1995 March 2 "Gay Men and AIDS" Larry Kramer, Gabriel Rotello, Dennis DeLeon; 2054-3466 CLGR Forum on sex clubs, Levin Osborne, Rotello 1995 February 16, 1995 March 2; 1995 February 16; YCALMSS722_0031; 1; 02:03:30 (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102337921)
      - Larry Kramer on "The Phil Donahue Show", 2/13/90, 1990 February; YCALMSS722_0032; 1; 00:57:53 (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102337939)
        This tape has Larry Kramer as a guest on the Phil Donahue Show.
      - Lucille Lortel Awards, 1993 May 17; YCALMSS722_0033; 1; 01:42:07 (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102337947)
      - Basic Instinct/SF Queer Nation protests, undated; YCALMSS722_0034; 1; 00:31:16 (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102337954)
      - Day One, 1993 March 28; YCALMSS722_0036; 1; 00:26:56 (Box 233, Item barcode 39002102337962)
        Restricted fragile material.
      - "Rights and Reactions" by Phil Zwickler and Jane Lippman, undated; YCALMSS722_0036; 1; 00:55:45; The in the first segment of the video is very low. The video is in poor condition. (Box 233, Item barcode 39002102337970)
      - Roger [McFarland] on Morton Downey Jr. Show, 1987; YCALMSS722_0037; 1; 01:01:12 (Box 233, Item barcode 39002102337988)
        This is an episode of "The Morton Downey Jr. Show". It includes a segment on whether people with AIDS should be quarantined.
      - Broadway Bares IV, Broadway Beat, undated; YCALMSS722_0038; 1; 00:49:32 (Box 233, Item barcode 39002102337996)
      - Donahue, #11172 - AIDS, YCALMSS722_0039; 1; 00:58:53 (Box 233, Item barcode 39002102338002)
  - Oversize Material, circa 1916-1998
    - Just Say No (from Writing Files), circa 1988 (Box 154 (Oversize))
    - The Normal Heart (from Writing Files), circa 1989 (Box 155 (Oversize))
    - The Normal Heart (from Writing Files), circa 1985-1989; 3 (Box 156 (Oversize))
    - AIDS General, Philadelphia, the movie (from Professional Papers and Research Material) (Box 157 (Oversize))
    - AIDS Activism, ACT UP (from Professional Papers and Research Material) (Box 157 (Oversize))
    - Research Material (from Professional Papers and Research Material), circa 1980s-1998 (Box 157 (Oversize))
    - Interviews of and Articles by Larry Kramer (from Professional Papers and Research Material) (Box 157 (Oversize))
    - Family Papers, Album (from Personal and Other Papers) (Box 158 (Oversize))
    - Family Papers, Art Prints (from Personal and Other Papers) (Box 158 (Oversize))
    - Family Papers, Photographic portraits (from Personal and Other Papers) (Box 158 (Oversize))
    - Family Papers, Scrapbook (from Personal and Other Papers) (Box 158 (Oversize))
    - Medical Records, X-rays (from Personal and Other Papers) (Box 159 (Oversize))
    - Other Papers, Awards (from Personal and Other Papers) (Box 159 (Oversize))
    - Other Papers, Honorary award, The Normal Heart theater event benefiting the Gay Men's Health Crisis (from Personal and Other Papers) (Box 159 (Oversize))
    - Printed Material, AIDS activism, posters (from Personal and Other Papers), circa 1980s (Box 160 (Oversize))
    - Printed Material, Various speaking events, posters (from Personal and Other Papers) (Box 160 (Oversize))
    - Printed Material, The Destiny of Me, posters (from Personal and Other Papers) (Box 160 (Oversize))
    - Printed Material, Faggots, posters (from Personal and Other Papers) (Box 160 (Oversize))
    - Printed Material, Four Friends, posters (from Personal and Other Papers) (Box 160 (Oversize))
    - Printed Material, The Normal Heart, posters (from Personal and Other Papers) (Box 160 (Oversize))
    - Printed Material, Women in Love, posters (from Personal and Other Papers) (Box 160 (Oversize))
    - Printed Material, Miscellaneous printed (from Personal and Other Papers) (Box 161 (Oversize))
    - Printed Material, Magazines (from Personal and Other Papers), circa 1958-1981 (Box 161 (Oversize))
    - Printed Material, Newspapers (from Personal and Other Papers), circa 1980s-1990s; 2 (Box 161 (Oversize))
    - Printed Material, Newspapers (from Personal and Other Papers), circa 1983-1985; 3 (Box 162 (Oversize))
    - Printed Material, Newspapers (from Personal and Other Papers), circa 1987-1989; 4 (Box 163 (Oversize))
    - Printed Material, Newspapers (from Personal and Other Papers), circa 1989-1992; 3 (Box 164 (Oversize))
    - Photographs, Family photographs (from Personal and Other Papers), circa 1920s-1960s (Box 165 (Oversize))
    - Photographs, Personal photographs (from Personal and Other Papers), 6 (Box 165 (Oversize))
    - Photographs, Kramer, Larry by Annie Leibovitz (from Personal and Other Papers) (Box 166 (Oversize))
    - Photographs, Personal photographs (from Personal and Other Papers) (Box 166 (Oversize))
    - Photographs, Women in Love (from Personal and Other Papers), 3 (Box 166 (Oversize))
    - Framed print of the poem "Bore," inscribed "Love, Charlie" (from Personal and Other Papers) (Box 167 (Oversize))
  - Rolled Storage
    - Family Papers, Certificates, Arthur Kramer / 1916 Class Reunion photograph, George Kramer (from Personal and Other Papers), circa 1950s-1960s (Box 168 (Oversize))
    - Family Papers, Certificates, Rea Kramer (from Personal and Other Papers), circa 1920s-1930s (Box 169 (Oversize))
    - Printed Material, Rolled posters, unsorted (from Personal and Other Papers) (Box 170 (Oversize))
    - Printed Material, Rolled posters, unsorted (from Personal and Other Papers) (Box 171 (Oversize))
    - Printed Material, Rolled posters, unsorted (from Personal and Other Papers) (Box 172 (Oversize))
    - Printed Material, Rolled posters, unsorted (from Personal and Other Papers) (Box 173 (Oversize))
    - Printed Material, Rolled posters, unsorted (from Personal and Other Papers) (Box 174 (Roll))
    - Wall Mural by Larry Kramer (from Personal and Other Papers) (Box 175 (Roll))
  - Broadsides
    - Printed Material, The Night Larry Kramer Kissed Me, poster (from Personal and Other Papers), circa 2000 (Box 176 (Broadside))
    - Printed Material, The Tragedy of Today's Gays, poster (from Personal and Other Papers), circa 2005 (Box 177(Broadside))
- July 2011 Acquisition, 2007-2011; 3.71; (8 boxes) + 1 broadside folder
  Organized into three series: I. Correspondence. II. Writings. III. Personal and Other Papers.
  - Correspondence, Series I
    - Unsorted Correspondence, 1999-2011; 23 (Box 187)
  - Writings, Series II
    - "Chapter 6: The curious case of Elmer Ellsworth," typescript, 2003 (Box 188)
    - "Chapter 7: Yours forever," typescript, 2003 (Box 188)
    - "Chapter 8: Marriage and Mary Todd," typescript, 2003 (Box 188)
    - "Chapter 9: Lincoln in perspective--three views," typescript, 2003 (Box 188)
    - "Homosexuals in Colonial America," draft, undated (Box 188)
    - "The Normal Heart," revised typescripts and associated materials, 2004 (Box 188)
    - "We are not crumbs; we must not accept crumbs," speech, typescript, 2007 (Box 188)
    - "I wanted to look at water...," drafts, undated (Box 188)
    - "Obama is not my president.." speech, typescript, 2010 (Box 188)
    - "Lambda Awards," speech, typescipt, 2010 (Box 188)
    - Notebooks, undated; 2 (Box 188)
  - Personal and Other Papers, 2001-2011; Series III
    - Personal
      - Medical-Family-Friends-Contacts, 2001; 2 (Box 188)
      - "Lee Pace," drawing, 2011 (Box 188)
      - "Liza's 50th Birthday," printed photograph album, 2009 (Box 188)
      - Photographs, 2009 (Box 188)
      - Portrait of Larry Kramer, photographs, undated
      - Dog license, dog tags, 2011 (Box 188)
      - Realia, undated; 2 (Box 188)
    - Financial Records, 2010
      - Royalties, 2008-2011 (Box 188)
      - Probate, 2008 (Box 188)
      - Taxes, 2008-2009; 3 (Box 188)
      - Financial Records, 2008-2010; 3 (Box 188)
    - Audio Visual Material, 2008-2009
      - "Excerpts from GMHC-Oral History," (CD), undated (Box 189)
      - "Out-Q in the morning," (CD), 2 copies, 2008 (Box 189)
      - Ryo Toyonaga, artist drawings, (DVD), undated (Box 189)
      - "Summer of the Stonewall," documentary, (DVD), 2009 (Box 189)
      - "Alan Ross, Texas Freedom parade," (DVD), 2009 (Box 189)
    - Printed Material
      - AIDS material, 2009-2010 (Box 190)
      - Newsweek Magazine, 2006 May 15 (Box 190)
        "AIDS at 25, a special report," includes article with Larry Kramer
      - "Nuremberg Trials for Aids," printed version, copy, undated (Box 190)
      - Playbill, 2004-2011 (Box 190)
      - Ryo Totonaga, printed artwork, 2005-2009; 2 (Box 190)
        Includes art books and printed versions of Totanaga's artwork
      - "Visual and musical responses to the Aids Crisis in the U.S: heightening societal awareness and inciting political action." typescript by Kaitlyn Greer, 2009 (Box 190)
      - "Women in Love," screenplay by William Ivory, annotated by Larry Kramer, 2009 (Box 190)
      - Pamphlets, brochures, 2009-2011; 3 (Box 190)
      - Posters, undated
      - Magazines, 2004-2011 (Box 190)
      - Unsorted material, 2008-2011; 4 (Box 190)
      - Clippings, 2004-2011; 4 (Box 190)
  - Oversize, 1974-2010
    - Portrait of Larry Kramer, photographs, undated (Box 191 (Oversize))
    - Clippings, 1974-2009; 3 (Box 192 (Oversize))
    - Posters, undated (Box 192 (Oversize))
    - Poster, undated (Box 193 (Broadside))
    - Framed Art, 2010 (Box 194 (Oversize))
    - T-Shirts, undated (Box 195 (Oversize))
- February 2016 Acquisition, 1981-2015; 17.33 linear feet; (17 boxes)
  Organized into four series: Writings, Writings by others, Correspondence, personal and other papers, and Electronic Media.
  - Writings, 7.58; (7 boxes)
    - "AIDS: The war is lost", 1990 (Box 196)
    - "American People Volume 1" drafts and notes (16 folders), undated (Box 196)
    - "American People Volume 1" drafts and notes (18 folders), undated (Box 197)
    - "American People Volume 1" drafts and notes (4 folders), circa 2003 (Box 198)
    - "American People Volume 1" galley proof, circa 2003 (Box 198)
    - "Breeders 1" draft, undated (Box 198)
    - Book proposals, undated (Box 198)
    - "Faggots" draft (5 folders), 1999 (Box 198)
    - "Faggots" draft, 2000 (Box 198)
    - "Four Friends" typescript, undated (Box 198)
    - "Just Say No" notes, reviews, and clippings, 1990 (Box 198)
    - "Late Bloomers" screenplay, undated (Box 198)
    - "Masturbov Gardens" draft, 1990 (Box 199)
    - "Minor Dark Age" draft, undated (Box 199)
    - Miscellaneous writings and notes (2 folders), undated (Box 199)
    - "New Beginning" draft, undated (Box 199)
    - "Normal Heart" screenplay and drafts (20 folders), circa 1986 (Box 199)
    - "Search For My Heart No Longer" drafts (2 folders), circa 1991 (Box 199)
    - "Sissie's Scrapbook" screenplay, undated (Box 199)
    - "Sissie's Scrapbook" screenplay, undated (Box 200)
    - "Women in Love" screenplay and drafts (6 folders), 2001-2002 (Box 200)
  - Writings by others, 1.08; (1 box)
    - "Lincoln" screenplay, undated (Box 200)
    - "Chinatown" screenplay, undated (Box 200)
    - Berman, Marjorie. "Intersection of Agitprop Theatre and AIDS Activism..." thesis, 2013 (Box 200)
    - Galassi, Jonathan--song lyrics, undated (Box 200)
    - Kaufman, Moises. "Three trials of Oscar Wilde" playscript, 2015 (Box 200)
    - "'Dr. Strangelove" or: How I Learned to Stop Worrying and Love the Bomb" screenplay, undated (Box 200)
    - Newspapers, magazines, and printed material, 1984-2015; 22 folders (Box 230)
    - Newspapers, magazines, and printed material, 1979-2015; 8 folders (Box 231)
    - Newspapers, magazines, and printed material, 1970-2015; 2 folders (Box 232)
  - Correspondence, personal and other papers, 3.92; (3 boxes)
    - Engraved dish/award for Roger McFarlane from Gay Men's Health Crisis, 1982 (Box 200)
    - Esquire cover plaque/award, 1984 (Box 200)
    - 80th birthday cards and notes, 2015 (Box 200)
    - Bracelet, undated (Box 200)
    - Yale commencement programs and related papers, 2015 (Box 200)
    - Correspondence, 1982-2015; 3 folders (Box 200)
    - Correspondence, 1985-2015; 2 folders (Box 200)
    - Diary, undated (Box 200)
    - Wishengrad family tree, 1981 (Box 201)
    - Financial papers, 2012-2014 (Box 201)
    - Flyers, undated (Box 201)
    - Itineraries, 1987, 2015 (Box 201)
    - Rea Kramer personal papers, 1960-1983 (Box 201)
    - Rea Kramer passports, 1984, 1995 (Box 201)
    - Eulogy and notes for Rea Kramer's funeral, circa 1996 (Box 201)
    - Legal papers, 2008 (Box 201)
    - Medical papers, circa 2014 (Box 201)
    - Notes, undated (Box 201)
    - Event passes, undated (Box 201)
    - Photographs, 2001, undated; 3 folders (Box 201)
    - Lapel pins, undated (Box 201)
    - Press releases, 1985-1987 (Box 201)
    - Research notes, circa 1987-1987, undated; 2 folders (Box 201)
    - Speeches, circa 1987-2004; 2 folders (Box 201)
    - Award certificates, 1993-2014 (Box 206)
    - New York Times newspapers, 1987 (Box 206)
    - Poster for Hotchkiss Gay/Straight Alliance event featuring Larry Kramer, 2013 (Box 206)
  - Electronic Media, 3.5; (4 boxes)
    Restricted fragile material. Access copies of digital files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - "(500) days of summer" screener DVD, 2009 (Box 202)
    - "9" screener DVD, 2009 (Box 202)
    - "Alice in Wonderland" screener DVD, undated (Box 202)
    - "All Good Things" screener DVD, 2010 (Box 202)
    - "Animal Kingdom" screener DVD, undated (Box 202)
    - "Anna Karenina" screener DVD, 2012 (Box 202)
    - "Another Year" screener DVD, undated (Box 202)
    - "Avatar" screener DVD, 2009 (Box 202)
    - "Anvil" screener DVD, undated (Box 202)
    - "Beasts of the Southern Wild" screener DVD, 2012 (Box 202)
    - "Beginners" screener DVD, 2011 (Box 202)
    - "Bernie" screener DVD, undated (Box 202)
    - "Better Life" screener DVD, 2011 (Box 202)
    - "Blue Valentine" screener DVD, 2010 (Box 202)
    - "Broken Embraces" screener DVD, undated (Box 202)
    - "Brothers" screener DVD, 2009 (Box 202)
    - "Capitalism: A Love Story" screener DVD, 2009 (Box 202)
    - "Cars 2" screener DVD, undated (Box 202)
    - "Channel Clublum Two 2004-2009" DVD (Box 202)
    - "Chasing Ice" screener CD (2 folders), 2012 (Box 202)
    - "Cloudy with a Chance of Meatballs" screener DVD, undated (Box 202)
    - "Company Men" screener DVD, 2010 (Box 202)
    - "Coralina" screener DVD, 2009 (Box 202)
    - "Crazy Heart" screener DVD, 2009 (Box 202)
    - "Creation" screener DVD, undated (Box 202)
    - "Disgrace" screener DVD, 2007 (Box 202)
    - "District 9" screener DVD, undated (Box 202)
    - "Divo" screener DVD, undated (Box 202)
    - "End of Watch" screener DVD, undated (Box 202)
    - "Eye of the Storm" screener DVD, 2012 (Box 202)
    - "Fair Game" screener DVD, 2010 (Box 202)
    - "Fighter" screener DVD, 2010 (Box 202)
    - "For Colored Girls" screener DVD (Box 202)
    - "For Greater Glory" screener DVD, undated (Box 202)
    - "Funny People" screener DVD, 2009 (Box 202)
    - "Ginger and Rosa" screener DVD, undated (Box 202)
    - "Girl with the Dragon Tattoo" screener DVD, undated (Box 202)
    - "The Grey" screener DVD, undated (Box 202)
    - "Half Nelson" screener DVD, 2007 (Box 202)
    - "Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows Part II" screener DVD, 2011 (Box 203)
    - "Hobbit: An Unexpected Journey" screener DVD, 2012 (Box 203)
    - "Hunger Games" screener DVD, 2012 (Box 203)
    - "Hurt Locker" screener DVD, undated (Box 203)
    - "I Am Love" screener DVD, 2010 (Box 203)
    - "I Love You Phillip Morris" screener DVD, 2010 (Box 203)
    - "Imaginarium of Dr. Parnassus" screener DVD, 2009 (Box 203)
    - "In the Loop" screener DVD, undated (Box 203)
    - "Inception" screener DVD, 2010 (Box 203)
    - "Inglorious Basterds" screener DVD, 2009 (Box 203)
    - "Inside Job" screener DVD, 2010 (Box 203)
    - "The Intouchables" screener DVD, 2012 (Box 203)
    - "Invictus" screener DVD, 2009 (Box 203)
    - "Irene in Time" screener DVD, 2009 (Box 203)
    - "Hangover" screener DVD, 2009 (Box 203)
    - "How Do You Know" screener DVD, undated (Box 203)
    - Jean-Luc Goddard Collection DVDs, 1982-1993 (Box 203)
    - "The Karate Kid" screener DVD, undated (Box 203)
    - "King's Speech" screener DVD, 2010 (Box 203)
    - "La Prima Cosa Bella" screener DVD, undated (Box 203)
    - "Late Quartet" screener DVD, 2013 (Box 203)
    - "Lightkeepers" screener DVD, undated (Box 203)
    - "Lincoln" screener DVD, undated (Box 203)
    - "Looper" screener DVD, undated (Box 203)
    - "Love + Other Drugs" screener DVD, 2010 (Box 203)
    - Paramount screener DVD pack (Lovely Bones, Up in the Air, Star Trek), 2009 (Box 203)
    - "Master" screener DVD, 2012 (Box 203)
    - "Mary and Max" screener DVD, undated (Box 203)
    - "Me and Orson Welles" screener DVD, 2010 (Box 203)
    - "The Men Who Stare at Goats" screener DVD, 2009 (Box 203)
    - "Les Miserables" screener DVD, 2012 (Box 203)
    - "Moonrise Kingdom" screener DVD, 2012 (Box 203)
    - "Mother and Child" screener DVD, undated (Box 203)
    - "The Music Never Stopped" screener DVD, 2011 (Box 203)
    - "The Night Larry Kramer Kissed Me" DVD, 2011 (Box 203)
    - "No Country for Old Men" screener DVD, 2007 (Box 203)
    - "Out in the Silence" DVD, 2009 (Box 203)
    - "Outrage" DVDs (2 folders), 2009 (Box 203)
    - "Pirate Radio" screener DVD, 2009 (Box 203)
    - "The Pirates! Band of Misfits" screener DVD, undated (Box 203)
    - "Please Give" screener DVD, 2010 (Box 204)
    - "Pirates of the Caribbean on Stranger Tides" screener DVD, 2011 (Box 204)
    - "Precious" screener DVD, undated (Box 204)
    - "The Princess and the Frog" screener DVD, undated (Box 204)
    - "Promised Land" screener DVD, 2012 (Box 204)
    - "Quartet" screener DVD, 2012 (Box 204)
    - "Running with Scissors" screener DVD, 2007 (Box 204)
    - "Salt" screener DVD, undated (Box 204)
    - "Saving Grace B. Jones" screener DVD, undated (Box 204)
    - "Sessions" screener DVD, 2012 (Box 204)
    - "A Serious Man" screener DVD, 2009 (Box 204)
    - "Shutter Island" screener DVD, 2010 (Box 204)
    - "Silver Linings Playbook" screener DVD, 2012 (Box 204)
    - "A Single Man" screener DVD, 2009 (Box 204)
    - "Skyfall" screener DVD, undated (Box 204)
    - "Smashed" screener DVD, undated (Box 204)
    - "Snow White and the Huntsman" screener DVD, 2012 (Box 204)
    - "Spinetingler!" The William Castle Story" screener DVD, undated (Box 204)
    - "Take Shelter" screener DVD, undated (Box 204)
    - "Taking Woodstock" screener DVD, undated (Box 204)
    - "Tangled" screener DVD, undated (Box 204)
    - "Tempest" screener DVD, undated (Box 204)
    - "This is 40" screener DVD, 2012 (Box 204)
    - "Tinker, Tailor, Solider, Spy" screener DVD, 2011 (Box 204)
    - "Touching Home" screener DVD, 2010 (Box 204)
    - "Two Lovers" screener DVD, 2009 (Box 204)
    - "Up" screener DVD, undated (Box 204)
    - "West of Memphis" screener DVD, 2012 (Box 204)
    - "Whatever Works" screener DVD, undated (Box 204)
    - "Win Win" screener DVD, 2011 (Box 204)
    - "Winter's Bone" screener DVD, 2010 (Box 204)
    - "The Wire" DVDs [Seasons 3-5], 2006-2008; (3 folders) (Box 204)
    - "Wrangler" screener DVD, undated (Box 205)
    - "Zodiac" screener DVD, 2007 (Box 205)
    - "Irene in Time" soundtrack, 2009 (Box 205)
    - Conversation with Montgomery fellow: Larry Kramer, 2012 (Box 205)
  - Audiovisual material, 0.42; (1 box)
    Restricted fragile material. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - "Question of Equality" VHS set, 1995 (Box 207)
      This VHS set is commercial. It has not been digitized.
- November 2016 Acquisition, 1960-2012; 20.67; (23 boxes)
  Organized into six series: Writings, Writings by others, Correspondence, personal and other papers, Diaries and notebooks, Electronic media, and Audiovisual materials.
  - Writings, 2.92; (7 boxes)
    - "The American People" drafts and notes, undated; 5 folders (Box 208)
    - "The American People" drafts and notes, undated; 5 folders (Box 209)
    - "The American People" drafts and notes, undated; 4 folders (Box 210)
    - "The American People" drafts and notes, undated; 5 folders (Box 211)
    - "The American People" drafts and notes, undated; 6 folders (Box 212)
    - "The American People" drafts and notes, undated; 5 folders (Box 213)
    - "The American People" drafts and notes, undated; 4 folders (Box 214)
    - "The Normal Heart" draft and notes, undated (Box 214)
  - Writings of others, 0.42; (1 box)
    - Black, Dustin Lance. "8" script, undated (Box 215)
    - Kramer, Arthur. "Memoir of an Ancient Yalie" draft, 2012 (Box 215)
  - Correspondence, personal papers, and photographs, 5.83; (10 boxes)
    Includes correspondence, event documentation, business and financial papers, theatrical programs, newsletters, press clippings, and personal papers.
    - Yale-related business papers, 2000-2001; 2 folders (Box 215)